hello
i'm aila we're going to make start
raving who's on that ice cream today
i've run many computations and have
concluded that the following is the most
favorable combination
a moscovado hazelnut ice cream with a
whiskey swirl
sir have you finished in there hey
don't embarrass me in front of the
wizards sir cork it
we have ingredients to buy
[Music]
well these hazelnuts and vanilla really
don't look great what should we use
instead
pyramid hazelnuts are considered the
best there are sir also madagascar and
tahitian vanilla
are widely considered the best vanilla
should i order some of each
yep go ahead what about my options for
gold so you can buy
gold spray gold glitter gold powder but
i would recommend
gold leaf should i place an order for
that also sir
yep buy it and what did tony start drink
mr stark liked many drinks sir but la
froi whiskey was a favorite
you can purchase that in your current
location
oh yeah i can see it down there it's the
select though
can you order some of the 10-year stuff
certainly sir consider it done
ooh a little baby bottle let's grab that
to try tonight
so you should really consider driving an
audi eat room did you mean to say that
out loud
[Music]
place your milk cream sugar and egg
yolks in a suitable pan
and gently heat to 77 degrees centigrade
then add your vanilla seeds and the pod
itself
finally add your frangelico alcohol and
store it
covered in your refrigerator
[Music]
heat the water and sugar swell don't
stir until your desired colour is
achieved
take off the heat and add your cream
mixture when combined
add a pinch of salt and your laphroaig
whiskey you can transfer this to a
heatproof container
ready for use
[Music]
remove the vanilla pod from your
prepared base and add your skimmed milk
powder and let it hydrate for 20 minutes
when your ice cream base is ready pour
it into your machine and churn
i like to call this machine vision
[Music]
do
when complete layer your pyramid
hazelnuts and whiskey swell
and leave in the freezer for 4 hours
before consuming
[Music]
some people have said that i look tired
in some of the videos
i am this is the reason why
say hello to ice cream fans
i don't know thanks for watching what is
so far possibly the most extravagant ice
cream making video
well certainly i've ever created but um
most probably that i've ever seen as
well
if you've not seen any of the iron man
films this t-shirt won't make any sense
because not only did he like
ac dc this obviously is a iron man it's
a black sabbath song but we'll ignore
that
let's just get the apron on i've got my
uh
iron man badge on there as well
stark raven hazelnuts no idea what it's
meant to be
no one knows out of end game as well
much like hunger hulk burn and fudge we
just know that it's a hazelnut based
thing
all right let's come up with all the
ingredients i'll pop the ingredients up
on the screen so people can actually see
what they are
and obviously one of the main flavors is
the whiskey this is obviously empty now
because
you've used it all but um laphroaig is a
really
peaty whisky i can't drink this stuff on
my own i'm not a big whisky fan
to be honest i prefer pike creek
canadian whiskey tastes like rum
that's what i prefer but if you make
this
use whiskey that you enjoy if you do a
smaller batch
that little 50 ml bottle will be enough
for you
but if you do a larger batch be prepared
for the expense to roll on through
because this is certainly not a cheap
ice cream to make
anyway let's um let's see if it's ready
eiler is
is the ice cream ready sir the physical
render is complete
okay
thanks isla laphroaig whiskey
just to touch on that again was one of
tony stark's
favorite drinks champagne sake whiskey
all of those kind of things i mean he
was a billionaire playboy philanthropist
so he was all about that kind of life
laphroaig is
what we think was in his massive super
amazing cooler
in the first iron man movies when he
releases the jericho missile for
demonstration
that's what's in there so let's get some
of this ice cream out into the bowl
and finish decoration off we're going to
finish decoration for this
and as mentioned earlier in the video
we're going to go for
some gold leaf i've never used this
stuff before
so your guess would be as good as mine i
know that they
usually not usually use you know a brush
and that to
to decorate but we are just literally
going to
tap that on top like that
and i've decanted some of the whiskey
sauce
and we are just going to
decorate the front of that
like so
[Music]
let's dive into this and see what it's
like
i like can you talk people through the
flavors
please tahitian vanilla is a subtle
flavour
it is allowing the hazelnut flavours to
dominate the frangelico is just enough
to enhance the pyramud hazelnuts
the laphroaig caramel sauce is very
strong and something mr stark
would have liked very much mr stark was
known for being subtle with his design
choices
wouldn't you agree sir
wow i don't really know what else to say
i hate the whiskey on its own it really
works in the ice cream
hazelnuts isla has already said it
this is off the chart thanks very much
for watching
if you want to see some more marvel
inspired ice creams hit the comments
below and let us know
this one is great but for now
thank you for watching it would be very
much appreciated if you would like and
subscribe to this channel
so should we start work on our black
widow ice cream